A Guide to the Lodged Surveys, A-Z, from the Virginia Land Office, 1745-1868
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Lodged Surveys from the Virginia Land Office, 1745-1868
The Library of Virginia
LOI 48
.7 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
Virginia. Land Office
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession LOI 48 transferred by the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1948.
Historical Information
The act which established the previous Land Office passed the General Assembly on 22 June 1779. The register was the head of the Office and was appointed by joint ballot of both houses of the legislature. The office of the Superintendent of Weights and Measures was abolished by an act of 7 February 1867, and his duties were transferred to the register of the Land Office. The records of the Land Office which were in the custody of the Secretary of the Commonwealth were transferred to the State Library, and, by Act of Assembly on 5 March 1952, the duties of the regsiter of the Land Office were transferred from the Secretary of the Commonwealth to the State Librarian.
Scope and Content
*****************
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Virginia. Land Office
Subjects:
Surveying -- Virginia.
Genre and Form Terms:
Land surveys -- Virginia; State government records -- Virginia
Contents List
- Lodged Surveys, 1745-1868., Extent: 2 boxes (0.9 cu. ft.). (Box 1-2)
  Alphabetical
  - Lodged Surveys, A, 1797-1860. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lodged Surveys, B, 1775-1861. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lodged Surveys, C, 1782-1861. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lodged Surveys, D, 1749-1859. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lodged Surveys, E, 1785-1861. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lodged Surveys, F, 1780-1867. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lodged Surveys, G, 1761-1848. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lodged Surveys, H, 1779-1866. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lodged Surveys, J, 1793-1832. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lodged Surveys, K, 1781-1860. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lodged Surveys, L, 1783-1859. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lodged Surveys, M, 1780-1866. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lodged Surveys, N, 1786-1858. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lodged Surveys, O, 1827. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lodged Surveys, P, 1745-1858. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lodged Surveys, R, 1786-1862. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lodged Surveys, S, 1774-1868. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lodged Surveys, T, 1796-1857. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lodged Surveys, W, 1775-1867. (Box 2, Folder 19)